EHSAN RAVI

Marietta, GA 30067

Phone: (678) 856-9033 | Email: ekhosr@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ehsan-khosravi-07492ab2 | Portfolio: github.com/ekhosr/myPortfolio

SUMMARY

Disciplined and dynamic payroll specialist with six years of experience in accounting and office management. strong administrative skills

Technical Skills

Payroll: ADP RUN, ADP Workforce, Personnel and Human Resources, Time and Attendance

Accounting: QuickBooks, Payroll Reporting, AR/AP, Data Analyst, PPP Forgiveness Application

Computer: Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL

Office Management: Time Management, Customer and Personnel Services, Marketing

Relevant Experience

Bookkeeper & Payroll Specialist 2019 – Current

Mandani Management LLC Atlanta, GA

Bookkeeper & Payroll Specialist 2016 – Current

Wish Wash LLC Atlanta, GA

Office Manager 2013 – 2016

E-Recycle USA Tucker, GA

Education

Web Developer Certificate: Georgia Tec Coding Bootcamp, Atlanta, GA

Java Programmer Certificate: Piedmont Technical College, Clarkston, GA

Computer Science: Azad University Mobarakeh, Isfahan, Iran